Hello everyone, welcome back to my channel, today I am going to show you how to hang your clothes on a shelf
I am going to show you how to hang your clothes on a shelf
you can see the shelf in the picture box
and the shelf of children
let's see how to hang your clothes on a shelf
open the window and you can see a shelf
let me move it up a bit
did you hear what Xiaofei said?
Can you guess who it is?
Friendship is a knight, we are iron partners
Then you can open the model and hang this dress on this dresser
And then the next thing is that you can also directly improve its quality
And then this dresser is a very ordinary dresser like this and then we have this kind of dresser for pants in our pants
And then there's this kind of dresser with a belt and a dresser with a towel
And then you can see that after you hang your clothes, you can also pull it
Because it's because this dresser is a virtual model, so when we finally improve the quality, we have to change its surface diameter to zero
This is a very ordinary dresser and then we look at this dresser
So you can see that if we are using this dresser
Then we need to draw a small plate here at the border
Well, wait a minute and then I'm going to put it here and I'm going to put it together
Take a look and move it over there
And then we're going to move it over there
And then I'm going to move it over here and I'm going to move it over here
I'm going to freeze it and then I'm going to open it and I'm going to be like this
I'm sorry, because I'm wearing a T-shirt, so it's a little smelly
Oh, good. We'll do it later
move it up a little bit
move it closer
we will move these two pieces
to the top of the frame
and move them up a little bit
we will fold this stripe
now its not wide enough
so I did it narrow
same as the frame
it looks better
please forgive me
i am a ao hour
Open the lid like this, and put the cloth on top of it.
After that, please ignore the sleeve, we will use a new piece of fabric to adjust the transparency of the fabric to 0.
This is the only way.
The other two ways are very simple.
The most important way is this one.
Let's see how to make a folded shirt.
The folded shirt is made directly from the mold.
There are two folded shirts here.
Let's take a look.
Oh, I didn't use 6.0.
I used 5.2.382 today.
Our 6.0 is out.
You can download it on the official website.
We can open it directly.
You can get some cloth items.
This is a full-fledged shirt.
Wait a minute.
Oh, I have a little card.
Let me get a glass of water.
Okay.
You can see that we have a full-fledged shirt here.
I will put it on it.
You can see these, uh, things about his front and back.
This is the first one.
I think we'll use this model.
Maybe it'll be a bit of trouble to have this in here.
That's right.
That's what it's about.
I'm going to have a new shirt.
Which color do you like?
You like white.
Now you can see that this folded shirt is ready to be used as a fabric.
You can choose different fabrics here, for example, the collar.
As long as it has a collar.
If you have to fold it, you can use a fixed needle and a thread to do it.
That's it.
Let's take a look.
This is our folded shirt.
If you have a table, you can just put it on the table and just fold it.
Next, let's do some other things.
For example, make a shelf and a mirror.
And...
As you can see on the poster, this is the window.
The shelf and the window are quite big.
So I...
So I just recorded a video.
If I do it on the spot, it might be a bit laggy.
I hope you can understand.
No?
Let's take a look at this video.
You can look at this video to see what's going on.
And then, if you do it on the spot, you can check the table, the mirror, the table.
And then, I'm going to show you how to do it.
Then let me show you the first step.
What I'm going to show you is this.
There are three ways of making the table.
The first way is to make a round table with the table.
And then adjust the distance between the table and the mirror.
Make the edge of the table a little bit more round.
Then edited it.
Making it fall on the table edge.
Let it fall on the ground to make it flat
Then adjust the thickness of the curve
It's online now, great
Now it can become a ball
Turn off the curve
This is a pillar
The thickness here is 180, which is 1.8 meters
Then change it to a metal one
Then change the color
Where is the scene?
The scene is in our company
But our scene is only open to business users
This is a pillar
This is the first way
Just add it directly and then do it
Then the second way
Let's take a look again
Let's copy a board
Adjust it to 0
You can see a board like this
A round board
After making this round board
I will turn this board into an OBJ
I choose to select
Count its name
Like this
You can take a look here
We choose to save the path to the original text
You can use any text
After doing it, we will move this page
After doing this, we will move this page
Let's look
Then give it a OBJ
Just the OBJ we just made
We just made the O hus
So we choose to add a導入的附件
After you import it
It's just like this
I will direct it to the one after that
I'll show you how to adjust the width and the diameter of it.
Sorry, I don't know what I was thinking when I was doing it.
This is the second way to make this pillar.
Use the board to make an OBJ component and then make this pillar.
The third way is to use a 3D shape file in the Emeta folder.
There is a 0.3 in the file, which is a pillar.
There is a 0.2 in the A, B, and C file, which is a virtual model.
As you can see, it's a pillar.
Turn it around.
Turn it up.
As you can see, this is a cylinder.
In the same way, we can adjust the Y, Y, and Z axis and make a cylinder.
Turn it over.
You can transfer to our WeChat official account to get a large gift bag.
This is a pillar made by a virtual model in our warehouse.
You can also set the material for it.
No one is talking to us.
This is the pillar I made.
You can see that the three pillars are made the same.
You can choose what you want to do.
It's hard.
It's hard to hold it.
We just need to leave two pillars to make a pillar.
You can transfer the benefits to our WeChat official account.
It should be a large gift bag.
Everyone should be looking forward to it.
Then make a round shape.
Make a base plate for it.
It's dead.
I didn't get to see it.
Our little Cijun is more lively today.
Do you want to chat with Cijun for a while?
Yes.
I also used the board here to make a base plate.
You can use what I just did.
This guy just said hello to me.
He is my student.
You put it in a back and adjust its side bend.
You need to make it a little rounder.
The plate is too far away, so it's a little ugly.
Then let's determine where to put the two pillars.
Draw a line, for example, three sections.
Then let's move its position.
Look at the shrimp.
Move its position.
These two long pillars are finished.
Now let's do something else.
Make a small pillar.
Because it is to hang things.
Our little C student also knows how to hang things.
Here it is.
Because it is to hang things,
we will make a smaller pillar.
I hope you can understand.
Then let's make a bigger one.
Like a small flat plate.
We will make a bigger one.
Then let's turn its direction.
Move it in one direction.
Now the first one is done.
The rest of the pillars can be
pasted directly.
Let's take a look at one of the beads that I've made before
You can see it's like this
Next, we're going to hang the scarf on top
You can also make the scarf in advance and make a shape
Just hang it up
Just make a shape on both sides
Let's take a look
Flash on my desk
I'll hang it on the desk
Let's hang another hat on the side
You can see it
This hat is also a very ordinary one that I made in advance
After you make the hat, you can just turn it around
Just a shape
You can listen to our 6.0 new song on the Internet next Friday
We have added a lot this time
You should be interested in the function
You can see that this is done
Then we directly open the suspense
Let's take a look
The hat is a hat made directly from the board
I'll show you after I finish the whole thing
This hat is actually made from the board
This is a complete and finished suspense picture
Let's take a look at how to make this mirror
Including the frame behind the mirror
It's not difficult either
It's also relatively simple
I also look forward to seeing you after this live broadcast
Next time when you send us a request
You can make some beautiful Chen Li
You see, we give the model a change of posture
First, this
vào
First, we give the model a change of posture
I just didn't get used to the clothes
But I took a live broadcast with this clothes
You guys can see our online
There will be a coins on Thursday
The prize is still quite rich
The prize is still quite rushing
Let's make paper first
Then we'll do something else
then we'll do something else
I'm going to make a floor plan first.
The floor plan is basically using a board and a table.
Draw a board first.
You can go to the website to see the computer configuration.
Where to draw the prize?
When you sign up for our live streaming, you will see the prize.
For the specific prize, we will notify you that day.
Let's turn on the model and the clothes first.
Let's see.
Let's simulate this board hanging on the floor.
We also need to add a pattern to it.
It's also a pattern with a floor plan.
Just pull it out directly.
Can you see it?
Let's give it a shiny color to make it look a little bit brighter.
It's a little bit brighter.
We have a winner on the official account.
You can check it out on the official account.
Now let's make this mirror.
Okay?
Friends.
Draw the height of the mirror first. This is an 80x1.8 meter mirror.
Let's take a look at it.
I won't share the materials today because they are quite simple.
You should learn it and do it yourself.
Then this mirror needs to be slightly slimmer.
Make the corner of the mirror.
And the corner of the bottom.
Now let's make the edge of the circle next to the mirror.
Draw a square for it.
Remember to change the mirror to a metal one.
So that it will reflect the light.
Then put the circle on it.
Remember to turn the other circles around.
Or freeze them.
So that it will look smoother as well.
Go to wait a moment.
Wait a moment.
Okay.
You can find our computer settings on the official website.
You can check it out on the official website.
Let's try to change the angle.
I just set it to 360.
It's too sharp.
Let's change the color.
Let's change it to a lighter color.
Now let's make the support frame.
Let's make a plate first.
A square plate.
It's the same as making a pillar.
You can do all three methods.
I'm using the world coordinates here.
The official website is
3w.close3d.com
I'm using a metal material.
Let's change it to black.
Let's see.
It's also to increase the rendering speed.
You can ask for help on the official website
if you have any questions.
Now let's change the length.
The first step is to
make the support frame.
Make sure you put the support frame
exactly as the frame.
Make it like this.
You don't want it to be too long.
It's not too long.
Just a little shorter.
Then move the position.
Place it almost that way.
学生买的话学生买的话会在官网有相应会自己可以看一下 Oh, the student version will be on the official website. You can take a look at it yourself.
做好一根以后另外一根直接复制出来就可以了直接平移就可以了 After you make one, you can just copy the other one out and then you can just flatten it out.
还有一个底下的支撑的那个脚 There's another one underneath that's supporting the foot.
大家可以看一下然后这个镜子就做好了 You can take a look at this mirror and it's done.
给大家看一下这个镜子鞋是可以照射到这个人的效果的 You can show it to everyone. This mirror can actually reflect the effect of this person.
镜子记得要用金属的一个材质啊 You have to remember to use a metal material for the mirror.
大家一定要记得这个就是我们渲染一个效果大家可以看一下 You have to remember that this is what we're going to show you.
今天我们来做这个做这个整个橱窗的一个展示 Now we're going to do this, this whole window display.
这个也是基本所有都是我用版片做出来的 This is basically all of this is made with my version
我们宽这里是我们宽这里是四米的高一米五的宽 We're wide here, four meters high, one meter and five meters wide.
做一个那个版片出来做一个那个版片出来做一个那个版片出来
看一下我们现在在搭那个橱窗的那个我们现在在搭那个橱窗的那个我们现在在搭那个橱窗的那个
那个整个橱窗的那个外框 直接复制版片然后给他旋转一个角度 I'm going to copy the board and rotate it around
那可以旋转视角去查看它不要把它撞歪点把它放到另外一个版片那个旁边去 You can rotate the view to check it out. Don't bend it a little bit. Put it next to the other board
嗯我们所有关于购买的东西大家可以去官网查看我们在这里就统一不做回答了啊 We're going to go to the official website to check out all the things we've purchased. We're going to do it here.
大家不要再问我们宽网买去买要多少钱可以直接去我们官网看官网网纸是3w点可乐3d点看大家不要再问我们宽网买去买要多少钱可以直接去我们官网看官网纸是3w点可乐3d点看
那这个外面四个边就搭好了还有上面一个顶跟底下一个拖底啊上面一个顶做一下这个外面四个边就搭好了还有上面一个顶跟底下一个拖底啊上面一个顶做一下
也都是用版片做的也都是用版片做的
看一下我们也是先把底做好继续看然后再做一个拖底拖底也是直接复制就可以了复制粘贴
然后直接给他加渲染厚度然后直接给他加渲染厚度
Also, we don't want the edge to be too far from each other
Let's adjust the resolution a little bit
We still have one inside and one inside.
Very fast.
What do you mean by very fast?
Time flies. It's almost Chinese New Year.
Yes, it's almost Chinese New Year.
We still have one inside.
It's almost Chinese New Year.
We are here to grab a job.
We still have one inside.
Every time I'm on Live,
the comments are so funny.
The comments are so funny.
I have to adjust it.
It's the same as the outside with enoughilles.
I don't have an mini-tool.
So, I just cut them on the fly.
I think I can give it a little bit of position
Select that version
Let's take a look
Add a change to the rendering
Or change it to the same as the two sides
It's also just a direct copy
Our live streamer has a lot of work to do today
Let's open the live streamer and see what's going on
Which work do you guys want to see next
We're going to make a frame for him because we're going to put a sign on top of it and then we're going to use this to measure it directly
Let's measure it first
Let's see how long and wide it is
We're going to measure it and then we're going to draw a rectangle
And then we're going to give him a little bit of position
And then we're going to move it down a little bit
And then I put it in there, and I'm here
Let's just show him why I'm sitting in the credits
The line is a little bit off
The line is up
Just adjust your position and you're good to go
Almost there
We'll add a sticker here.
Everyone wants to see me make furniture.
I really want to emphasize woodworking.
Let's draw the logo below.
Let me show you.
There's a layer here.
You can add the thickness here.
Remember to turn off the distance.
Let me check.
Okay.
I'm almost done.
If there's still half left,
you can just copy and paste it.
Let me show you what I've done before.
I've done this before.
Let me show you.
It's two like this.
Just delete the other one.
I can change the frame to metal.
It will look like this.
I'll add a sticker on this piece.
这个帘子,下下子直播我给你们提啊,大家想看做个帘子。
那位好老实的,我真的好不习惯啊。
把贴图拉大这样就可以了,我们在这里也会给它换成shiny的一个材质,让它看起来稍微有点光泽感。
往底下那个,还有底下一个放贴图的一个小的一个版片,大家也不要忘记。
我在这里给它加上这样的一个贴图,也是给它拉大就可以了。
我这些贴图都是PNG格式的。
给看一下。
然后是直接给它复制粘贴到另一个版片上就可以了。
然后给它换一个颜色,然后再给它,也是给它一个shiny的。
这个是试衣垫吗?不是试衣垫吗?
这个嘛,这个是橱窗。
宝贝们,这个是橱窗。
如果你想搭个框子做试衣垫也行嘛。
上面加个杆子,然后加一个面料。
做窗帘就好了。
橱窗把窗帘做个帘子拉起来有点不太好吧。
我会在这里也给它加上一个贴图。
我以为是鞋,鞋柜也行啊。
再多加两个几个版片做个风格嘛。
然后把鞋子放上去就可以了。
觉得快的可以后面看回放。
做鞋子可以把这个外面这个变成一个塑料的那种材质,稍微调透明一点就可以了。
然后给它加上一个纹理。
这里的贴图我可能加错了。
我们会给它换成一个,换一个,我们换一个png格式的。
我们七天以后会有回放放出来。
快吗?
我们七天以后B站再见。
对哦,七天以后刚好是我们的线上的那个交流大会,大家可以来看一下。
参加一下抽奖嘛,说不定那个幸运的锦鲤就是你呢。
换个影子。
门把手怎么做,你们真的要抢掉木工的活吗?
好,那这个外面的这个箱子我们就给它做的差不多了。
然后我们再看一下有没有哪个地方需要给它换个纹理。
然后我们可以把其中某一片吧,看一下啊。
我们把后面这个最大的这一片换一个纹理吧。
我们先换旁边那片,换个颜色。
我们在抽奖颜色底下会有两个选项,关于两个影子的一个选项,大家可以看一下。
格罗的公司在上海哦,亲爱的朋友。
再调一下下面一个。
然后我们给它加一个发线,在这里我们软件可以自动生成的。
包括换一个颜色。
给看一下这个纹理感。
把那个下面关于这个影子的强度再稍微调一下。
大家可以看一下。
我们再换一下旁边那个大的那个长方形的一个纹理。
看一下。
我也是给它冲淡一下纹理。
然后调整一下这个纹理的一个大小。
怎么还有直播来,我底下问有没有自己公司人呢。
大家可以看一下这个这个橱窗整体就搭的差不多了。
那你先告诉我们你哪个公司的嘛。
然后我们再为你寻找你同公司的人好不好。
我知道你是谁了。
哈哈哈。
这是我上周刚过期的那家公司。
然后我们把这个整个箱子另存一下。
然后我们再来看另外一个。
我想做好它还有人吗。
还有人要放进去吗。
我们来先打开一个人。
那这位为后。
9138的这一位。
您姓什么。
然后我确认一下您是哪一位。
哦,给我呀。
大家可以看一下这个人啊。
虽然是一个力症的姿势。
阿是不。
阿土不。
好的,好的,我知道了。
好的,好的,老婆。
你看一下我们把这个XR的关节点打开,就可以对这个模特进行编辑,它的关节点。
大家可以看一下,因为它腿上有个七根啊。
看到它这个是被锁定了它的方向和旋转。
这个书我有看过我上一期那个关于模特的直播的话,大家应该都会知道。
再关掉就好了。
然后我们来调整一下它这个腿的这个角度。
看一下。
调整好之后我们可以随时按下快递键X,那个Shift的JRX看一下它整个凹的那个造型啊。
我们先凹一只腿。
好。
然后我们再把整个模特稍微往后倾斜一点点。
那东哥你就慢一点调吧,你把它们调骨折了那可得了。
东哥是会来参加我们的线下交流会对吗?
我们再瞧瞧他的手啊。
确定一下哪只手不要点错了。
要骨折了可还成。
你们一调就变怪物的话,你就稍微调一点点,然后随时按一下Shift的JRX键看一下它们整个皮肤的表面。
然后这个手我们有一个握起的一个字上,调整一下这个手的表面。
手指头。
调骨折了可还成。
接着我们会关闭关节点去调整,让大家看一下。
噢我使用的不是6.0喔,我使用的是5.2。
6.0的功能还是很强大的。
因为一个个调太慢了,所以就不调了。
大家调好之后可以直接给它另存为姿势了。
After that, you can save it as a post
Next time, you can just open it and use it
Then I open a file again
You can see that I didn't change it here
Because this one is slower
Then we just open the post here
Then choose the post we just saved
You want to post it on the spot
Let everyone take a look
Then this one will follow the posture itself
Because all the particles here are 5
So it will move a little slowly
There is a little bit of no simulation in this corner
Let's open the simulation and simulate it again
Next time, you can reduce the quality of the clothing before changing the posture
Otherwise, it will be a little slower like me
Now you can come to our press conference
You can see the strength of our 6.0 function
Then drag the button down
And come to our 5.0
So for a little while, I just faced it
I'm not afraid that you will do it
Don't be afraid
I look in the mirror
It's just good
Have you got the normal播
You can check out our 6.0 new features on the website.
Yes, I'm using a notebook now.
Please.
Yes, that's a good idea.
I'm using a notebook now.
How do people in the mirror reflect light?
Hello everyone, thanks for your time and attention.
I even made an iPhone 12 for her.
An iPhone 12.
You can also make it yourself, you can just make a video for him
For the mirror, you can just use metal material
Use metal material to make it, and then
When it's diluted, it will appear
This is the way we choose to save the GIP
Then let's open this up for him
Then put that
I just poured it, I poured it in for him
Just that piece of clothing
Yes, mirror reflection can be done so well
Can you try it
This is what we pour in as a component
This component is a bit big
I am just making a small amount
Have you ever seen me here
Have seen all the 97 live broadcasts
Our little boy has seen it
Let's rotate the model
Let's rotate it
Are you curious how this sunglasses works?
Let's reveal it first
No, I won't reveal it
No one cares about me
Everyone is really interested in this sunglasses
One person cares about me
This sunglasses is also made of film
After the film is done, just tilt the OVJ
Adjust its transparency
OK
Thank you, Dongge
Adjust its transparency
Let me see
It's a little transparent
One is done
If you want to be a model
You have to use this method
Why is there someone laughing at the phone?
Don't do this to me
This is the OVJ model that I made today
Just tilt it and use it
It's the same as the model
Just open the pose
What is the experience?
You can watch the basic live stream on that live stream
The 5th or the last live stream
Anyway, it should be a live stream with details
I don't know if you are not an old fan
Dongge is so strict
This is also with us
The model is in the same position
Everyone is flying
Just turn a little bit
You can adjust the angle yourself
It doesn't affect me
It's good to chat with me
There is a material on the WBJ
So you need to fill it up one by one
I will give this pearl
A material of silk
No effect
Not stuck
I can't afford this ball
You are so good
You can't fly
What is this
I can't fly
I'm sorry
My glasses are also À
It's also to adjust
It keeps following me
My ears are still sore
Are you making things difficult for them?
You're making things difficult for me too.
The model is done.
Let's do the other manager's thing.
Plastic.
That's plastic material.
Plastic is more important than plastic.
Look at it.
We're making three hands.
You can go to another 3D model and make this.
The hands are a little crinkly.
Let's adjust the size and zoom in so you can see it better.
It's a little dark now.
It looks a little scary.
What do you think of this fashion lover?
Let's adjust the color and the nails.
My hands and nails are separated.
Pink nails.
We don't share all the materials.
What's wrong with this hand?
Let me see.
I'll put my hands in later.
You can find another one in other 3D software.
This is pretty simple.
This pose is a little small.
I can't see what it is.
It's a grab pose.
I can't say grab.
I don't know what it is.
Let me see.
We're going to adjust the height and position of the hand.
You look scared.
I'm sorry I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
I scared you.
It's my fault.
I'm going to make a white sugar milk candy next time.
I'll make you a white sugar milk candy next time.
I can't.
Why did I say it was just my hand?
Does my hand look bad now?
It's a little bit darker than the original color.
I'll adjust the color later.
It's okay. Just give everyone free courage.
Okay?
You don't charge everyone.
Free courage.
I'll adjust the color later.
Okay?
Okay.
I'll adjust the color later.
It's better than the original color.
When the color is white, it still looks good.
I'll adjust the color later.
Okay?
Sorry, I'll let you guys take a look at it.
My phone is broken.
It's my fault.
It's because I downloaded an OBJ from another 3D software.
So, I'm sorry.
We just downloaded a virtual model.
I'm not afraid of it.
It's just a toy.
Put a bunch of it in.
You're a bit cruel.
I mainly use my hand to hold the bag.
A bunch of it.
I'm afraid I'll be kicked out of the live stream.
It's almost done.
It's like a poster.
If you have time,
if you're more creative,
light it up.
It's about to be done.
Don't report me.
I'm very innocent.
This is the first hand.
I'll put it on.
Here you go.
Put it on my eyes.
What about your-
What do I do?
露台, 谢谢。
It's okay if you put it in reverse, our virtual model can also be in reverse, but I don't have a reverse fire here
Look, this is a bag, a bag, because I'm going to put that bag in his two hands, which is in the middle, so that he has a fixed one
Because I'm going to simulate it later, so I need to make my bag and his virtual model have a conflict, so I turned this OBJ into a virtual model
And I just, those two, Feifei, because they don't need to have a conflict, so I turned it into a copy
You see, I'm stuck now
You can take advantage of me so much
Turn around and take a look. It seems to be pulled over there. Just pull it a little bit
Oh, yeah, all the bags are made of board
In addition to this hand and the virtual model, all the other ones are made of board
Oh, and the head of the necklace is also a copy. In fact, they are all board
A beautiful girl and a sweet little fairy
This hand
Don't you like this hand
Is it over? No, we actually don't have much time to set up
People see the pot mood
I'll call him back later
There's a bag bag without a selection
And then there's another one. You can see that it's all made of board here. I've got a lot of content here
It's a corner and then we put that on and that's it. This bag bag is pulled out of it with a fixed needle in advance
What about this one
Just put it on and it looks like it's about the same
Basically didn't touch
Take a look at this one. It's all done. In the end, we can add a little light and then we can just do it
Let's take a look at the effect of this
Look at this card
I'm going to take a look at this one
Is there really just a little bit of it
Take a look at this. This is what I'm doing right now
You want to do this too
But I think this is pretty simple
How many years does this take to practice
You can try it yourself and then
And then we're going to get into our QA session. Do you have any questions for me today
Can you see the hat hat you want to see the hat
Okay, wait a minute. Let me look for it
It's right here
You can add lights in the kitchen
You can use the version to add lights directly from the type
You can also add it from the place where you have a round light or a round light
I also said
All right, let's take a look at this hat
This hat is what I use
Is a flat side
You see
Take a look
And then this hat
We also use a flat side
Take a look
This hat is what we do
It's a clothing file
Save it and then just rotate it like this
What else is there a question
What are the mirrors
Mirror is actually pretty simple too
I'm going to turn the light back on
Turn the light back on
I'm going to draw a board for you guys
The hat is not too bad, it's not too difficult
I'm also going to draw a board
This one
You can take a look
Wait a minute
I'm going to draw it
I'm going to use another one
You have to adjust it to a metal material
You have to remember to adjust it to a metal material
Like this
Then we can just open our wire
What material do you choose for the hat?
Do you choose the material according to the fabric you use?
I'm stuck
Oh, it's back on
I just want it to be a little faster
Wait a minute, I'm stuck again
I can't put it between the cold-cold board and the board
I can't have any conflicts
Hey, what's the problem you're asking me now?
How can the mirror reflect
You can take a look
Just make it into a metal material
This mirror will reflect
Because I'm a little lower on the pixels
I bought this computer
It's the hidden elf from the map
You can just add some metal to it.
But if you want it to be brighter, you can turn it down to 0.
But if it's not bleaching, you can't really see it.
So it has to be bleached.
What else is there? Oh, I hit my foot again.
My CPU is burning.
My friends.
There's actually a light in the window.
If you want to use a light, you can use the material in the board to choose the light.
And you can also add it to the bleeding area.
There's a sphere light, sphere light, and this kind of laser light.
Square light, IES light, and skylight light.
You can add them all by yourself.
Can the computer burn eggs?
Let me touch it and tell you.
It's fast.
How can a lot of clothes be placed in a row?
Aren't you just like my hat?
You're just like Teng Weiqiu.
Friends.
Or are your clothes wearing models?
Do you only have clothes or are your clothes wearing models?
Why is my hat so black and clear?
What kind of strange question is this?
Friends.
Is it very clear?
Take a look.
It's mainly because my face is clear.
It's very clear.
Yes, you remember to add something clearer.
Take a look at this.
Butterfly.
Let me take a look.
Butterflies are in our library.
If you don't want to do it, you can go straight from the library to find these butterflies.
Look, this is my butterfly.
Can you see it?
This is a stone.
Let me show you a butterfly.
Can you make a butterfly?
Yes, you can.
But my friend, my subway is about to run out.
What are you doing?
You are making things difficult for me.
You can find it directly from this library.
It's all available.
You can take a look.
This is the butterfly I'm using.
Take a look.
I'll open it for you to take a look.
I have this.
I have a ZPSC file here.
You can open it and use it directly.
My teacher doesn't have a boyfriend.
My teacher is a single dog.
I don't have a boyfriend even if I don't match him.
Take a look.
This is the butterfly.
The position is different.
I'll put it like this.
You'll know.
Yes, this is the butterfly.
You can just use this fake sewing tool to sew it up later.
It's not dirty.
You can use it if you want.
You can't use it without any clothes on and without a mask.
Even if you wear a mask,
Your clothes won't be dirty.
I'll try to use this one.
The first is this one.
Look at this.
This is a bunch of black clothes.
You may see the black clothes.
If the black clothes turns black,
If you add that,
Are you not clean in text?
And then there is your,
This,
I'll try to find it.
This is your color.
I don't know if the RGB value is 0.
You should take a look at this.
You mean you can rotate the view 90 degrees like this, right?
If you press Shift, you can actually feel a small hole.
It's a 90-degree or 45-degree hole.
If 4.2 version doesn't have this, you can upgrade it.
Now we've upgraded to 6.0, right?
Let's see how it works.
Why doesn't the material fall off at home?
I've already demonstrated it.
If you add a transparent sheet into it, it will freeze.
Many clothes are hung in a row.
If you turn the clothes into an OBJ,
which means it's in this area,
you can move your clothes with your virtual model.
Then you can hang it up.
Is there any problem?
If there is no problem,
our live broadcast will end at 5.20.
It will end at 9.20.
Oh, it will end at 9.20.
Sorry.
Can the butterfly be stored with the white board?
Or do you want to put it on the board?
You mean...
You...
This student of mine...
Do you mean you want to put it on the board?
Do you need to put it on the board with the board?
Friend?
Yes.
He said it's like selling clothes at the mall.
What's the problem?
It's just hanging a row of clothes.
It's like making each piece of clothing into a clothes rack.
Yes.
And then put it in one by one.
It's like hanging it on the clothes rack first,
then turning it into an OBJ,
and then putting it out one by one.
After you finish the rack,
you can put the OBJ in one by one.
That's it.
Do you want to practice it?
Yes.
You can practice it first.
Then you can put it out one by one.
Good.
You can add clothes every time.
Yes.
Like coming out of a clean net.
That friend of mine,
Weihao9138...
He said the cloth should be full.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Does it mean to put it on the board?
Or what?
Or is it just that clothes have to be full,
and then...
Next question,
the student said that the ratios should be full.
I'm not sure.
I don't know, I also heard that the Butterfly Sisters need to put a code
Different sizes of styles
Just go out and select it as a clothing file
Yes, yes, yes, you just select this model
Then you save it as a clothing file
Then just type it in and use it next time
Yes, as long as the Butterfly Sisters file
Don't have models
So I think it's better to just save it as a clothing file
Do you guys have any questions?
No problem!
Then I'll do the preview again
How do you want to express how you want to do it as you get older?
Is this the question?
Dear friends
The waistband with different width is smaller
You can also change the size of the waistband
You can change the size of the waistband
It's almost the end of our first live stream
My dear friend, our live stream is almost over
You're so cute
Next time we'll be doing a more complex version of this
Because a lot of people who watched our live stream
wanted us to do a more complex version
Those of you who watched our live stream
should know that I made a very simple one
What is this?
Yeah!
This silly girl loves instant noodles
You saw it, you saw it
Please look forward to our new 6.0 feature
How do you add more layers?
This selection...
This version
Sorry, I'm in a group
Is there a sticky xiaobao at the bottom?
Just click on sticky
Don't forget to join our 6.0
You can check it out
It's from 1pm to 5.30pm next Friday
This is the whole process
You can...
If...
If you can't join our live stream
You can sign up for our live stream
And you'll get a lucky draw
You have to fill out the real information
It's...
Yeah, it's your real information
And then
You can scan the code to sign up
And then on our WeChat official account
You can scan the QR code at the bottom of our live stream
The WeChat official account
This Ling Yi socks
Don't touch me
Who on earth are you?
You can scan the QR code
Scan the QR code at the bottom left corner of our screen
And then...
Send it to our WeChat official account
You'll get a lucky draw
For more details
You can check out our official account
This is the end of our live stream
We wish you all a happy weekend
Are you in Minghang?
Yes, we're in Minghang
Xiao Xi Jun, do you want to wish you all a happy weekend?
Wish you all a happy weekend
Bye bye
You're talking so well
Wish you all a happy weekend
Bye bye
You're talking so well